Finding Aid for G.M. (Gerard M.) Faeth papers, 1964-2005
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Research 1983-2005
  - National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST-formerly National Bureau of Standards (NBS) 1975-2004
    - Mixing and Radiation Properties of Buoyant Luminous Flame Environments
      - Quarterly Technical Reports September 1994-December 2000 (Box 6)
    - Non-luminous Flame Radiation in Turbulent Axisymmetric Flames
      - Annual Report undated (Box 6)
    - Radiation and Transport Properties of Fires
      - Proposal and Supporting Materials 1997-1998 (Box 6)
    - Radiation from Turbulent Luminous Flames
      - Annual Reports 1986-1991 (Box 6)
      - Correspondence 1988 (Box 6)
      - Monthly Progress Report April 1992 (Box 6)
      - Proposals 1985-1990, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Quarterly Technical Reports March 1986-May 1991 (Box 6)
    - Round Turbulent Non-buoyant Jets and Buoyant Plumes in Crossflow
      - Correspondence 2003-2004 (Box 6)
      - Proposal 2004 (Box 6)
    - Self-Preserving Mixing Properties of Steady Round Non-buoyant Turbulent Jets in Uniform Crossfows
      - Final Report 2004 (Box 6)
    - Self-Preserving Properties of Round Turbulent Non-buoyant Puffs and Starting Jets and Buoyant Thermals and Starting Plumes in Uniform Crossflow
      - Annual Report (part 2 of 2) 2002 (Box 6)
    - Soot, Carbon Monoxide, and Radiant Emissions from Flames
      - Annual Reports 1992-1994 (Box 6)
      - Correspondence 1993-1994 (Box 6)
      - Monthly Progress Reports May 1992-September 1994 (Box 6)
      - Proposal and Supporting Materials 1991-1993 (Box 6)
      - Quarterly Technical Reports September 1991-February 1994 (Box 6)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF) 1993-1997
    - Preferential-Diffusion/ Stretch Interactions in Laminar Premixed Flames
      - Progress Reports 1995-1997 (Box 6)
      - Proposal and Supporting Materials 1993-1994, 1997 (Box 6)
      - Proposal Reviews 1993-1994, undated (Box 6)
  - Office of Naval Research (ONR) 1986-1998
    - General
      - Correspondence 1989-1993, 1998 (Box 6)
      - Financial Documents 1989-1990, 1996 (Box 6)
      - Progress Reports (various projects) 1986-1991, 1996 (Box 6)
      - Publications/ Patents/ Presentations Honors Report 1992-1994 (Box 6)
    - Soot Properties During Turbulent Non-premixed Combustions of High-Energy Fuels and Air
      - End of the Fiscal Year Letter Reports 1994-1997 (Box 6)
      - Proposal and Supporting Materials 1992 (Box 6)
    - Supersonic Multiphase Mixing Layers
      - Project Summaries 1989, undated (Box 6)
    - Turbulent Premixed Flames at High Pressures
      - Budget Modification Forms 1987-1991 (Box 6)
      - Proposal and Supporting Materials 1987, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Renault Corporation/ University of Michigan Cooperative Research Program, September 1996-December, 1997
    - Primary Atomization of Liquid Jets
      - Final Report December 1997 (Box 7)
      - Monthly Progress Reports September 1996-July 1997 (Box 7)
  - Taitech, Inc. 1999-2004
    - General
      - Correspondence 2000, 2002 (Box 7)
      - Progress Reports September 2002-January 2004 (Box 7)
    - An Advanced Model for Aerated-Liquid Jets in Subsonic Crossflow
      - Proposals (Phase I and II) 1999-2000 (Box 7)
    - Development of Frequency Modulated Aerated-Liquid Atomizers
      - Proposal 2000 (Box 7)
    - Dynamics of Breakup of Aerated-Liquid Jets in Supersonic Crossflows
      - Final Report 2004 (Box 7)
      - Proposal and Supporting Materials 2002-2004 (Box 7)
    - Structure and Breakup of Aerated-Liquid Jets in Subsonic Flows
      - Proposal and Supporting Materials 2000-2001 (Box 7)
- Presentations, Publications, and Reviews 1985-2005, undated
  Presentations, Publications, and Reviews, 1985-2005 and undated, (3.0 linear feet) is a chronologically arranged sequence containing the presentations, writings, and proposal reviews of Faeth. Also included in this series are outlines of various research presentations, as well as bids and proposals for the Combustion and Flame book contract in 2002. Of particular note is the paper Structure of Round, Fully Developed, Buoyant Turbulent Plumes, which won the Best Paper Conference Award at the 29th National Heat Transfer Conference in 1993, as well as Turbulence Generation by Drops in Dense Sprays, which Faeth gave as the invited Andrew H. Hines Jr. Lecturer on November 7, 2002 at the University of Florida, Gainesville. This series also includes Professor Faeth's undelivered 2005 Distinguished University Professorship Lecture, entitled Search for the Mechanisms of Pollutant Soot Formation and Destruction in Flames.
  - Undated
    - [Untitled] (incomplete) (Box 7)
    - [Flame Structure] (incomplete) (Box 7)
    - [Non-turbulent Primary Breakup] incomplete (Box 7)
    - [Secondary Breakup] incomplete (Box 7)
    - [Soot Structure] (incomplete) (Box 7)
    - [Turbulent Premixed Flames] with photos (incomplete) (Box 7)
    - [Turbulent Primary Breakup] incomplete (Box 7)
    - Aerodynamic Effects on Primary and Secondary Breakup of Sprays (Box 7)
    - An Experimental Study of Flame/ Stretch Interactions for Premixed Hydrogen/ Air Flames (Box 7)
    - Compressible Multiphase Mixing Layer (incomplete) (Box 7)
    - Dispersed-Phase Structure of Pressure-Atomized Sprays at Various Gas Densities (incomplete) (Box 7)
    - Dynamics of Drop Deformation and Formation During Secondary Breakup in the Bag Breakup Regime (Box 7)
    - Effects of Pressure and Composition Variations on Laminar Premixed H20/O2/N2 Flames (Box 7)
    - Flamelet Concepts and Turbulence Interactions for Non-premixed and Premixed Flames (Box 7)
    - Fractal Projected Structure Properties of Soot Aggregates (Box 7)
    - Measurements and Numerical Simulations of Turbulent Premixed Flames (Box 7)
    - Preferential Diffusion Phenomena in High Reynolds Number Turbulent Premixed Flames (Box 7)
    - Preferential-Diffusion/ Stretch Interactions in Laminar Premixed Flames (Box 7)
    - Premixed Turbulent Hydrogen-Air Flames at High Reynolds Number (Box 7)
    - Primary and Secondary Liquid Breakup in Sprays (Box 7)
    - Primary Breakup of Round Pressure-Atomized Sprays (Box 7)
    - Self-Preserving Properties of Round Turbulent Thermals and Starting Plumes in Uniform Crossflow (Box 7)
    - Self-Preserving Vortical Structure of Turbulent Jets and Plumes in Crossflows (Box 7)
    - Soot Formation in Hydrocarbon / Air Laminar Jet Diffusion Flames (Box 7)
    - Soot Formation in Laminar Premixed Ethylene/ Air Flames at Atmospheric Pressure (Box 7)
    - Soot Formation in Weakly Buoyant Acetylene-Fueled Laminar Jet Diffusion Flames Burning in Air (Box 7)
    - Soot Nucleation and Growth in Acetylene Air Laminar Coflowing Jet Diffusion Flames (Box 7)
    - Soot Point Properties and Shapes of Non-buoyant Laminar Plane Jet Diffusion Flames (Box 7)
    - Soot Properties in Laminar Coflowing Jet Diffusion Flames (Box 7)
    - Spray Structure and Liquid Breakup Properties (Box 7)
    - Stochastic Simulation of Free Turbulent Premixed Flames in Isotropic Turbulence (Box 7)
    - Structure and Mixing Properties of High-speed Multiphase Mixing Layers (Box 7)
    - Turbulent Gas Jets in Liquids (Box 7)
    - Turbulent Hydrogen Air Flames at High Pressure (Box 7)
    - Turbulent Jet Experiments and Modeling (Box 7)
    - Turbulent Premixed Flames at Neutral Preferential-Diffusion Conditions: Measurements and Numerical Simulations (incomplete) (Box 7)
    - Turbulent Premixed Flames in Isotropic Turbulence: Measurements and Numerical Simulations (incomplete) (Box 7)
    - Turbulent Primary Break-up of Pressure-Atomized Sprays (Box 7)
  - 1980
    - Flame Phenomena August 21-22, 1985 (Box 7)
  - 1990-1994
    - Transport and Shock-Wave Interactions in Supersonic Multiphase Mixing Layers March 28, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Carbon Monoxide and Soot Emissions from Liquid-Fueled Buoyant Turbulent Diffusion Flames 1991 (Box 7)
    - Structure, Breakup, and Turbulence Interactions of Sprays July 19, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Laminar Burning Velocities and Transition to Unstable Flames in H2/O2/N2 and C3H8/O2/N2 Mixtures 1992 (Box 7)
    - Near-Limit Drop Deformation and Secondary Breakup 1992 (Box 7)
    - Particulate and Pollutant Emissions Properties of Non-premixed Flames April 1993 (Box 7)
    - Breakup and Turbulence Generation in Dense Sprays June 5-10, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Computational Evaluation of an Approximate Theory for the Optical Properties of Soot September 8, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Hydrodynamic Effects on Soot Formation within Non-premixed Hydrocarbon/ Air Flames August 29-31, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Hydrodynamic Suppression of Soot Emissions in Laminar Diffusion Flames, December1994 (Box 7)
    - Opportunities and Challenges of Combustion in Microgravity 1994 (Box 7)
    - Research Issues in Premixed and Non-premixed Combustion August 8-9, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Structure of Round, Fully Developed, Buoyant Turbulent Plumes May 1994 (Box 7)
  - 1995 (Box 8)
    - Drop Formation and Breakup Due to Shock Wave and Steady Disturbances 1995 (Box 8)
    - Drop Formation and Secondary Breakup Near the Thermodynamic Critical Point June 15, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Dynamic Properties of Secondary Break-up January 1995 (Box 8)
    - Effects of Hydrodynamics on Soot Formation Hydro-carbon Fueled Laminar Opposed-Jet Diffusion Flames October 16-18, 1995 (Box 8)
    - [Evaluation of Simulation Approximations] April 18, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Markstein Numbers and Unstretched Laminar Burning Velocities of Hydrogen-Air Flames, (incomplete) 1995 (Box 8)
    - Soot Morphology and Optical Properties in Flame Environments March, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Soot Morphology and Optical Properties in Non-premixed Turbulent Flame Environments 1995 (Box 8)
    - Soot Properties During Turbulent Non-premixed Combustion of High-Energy Fuels and Air October 11-13, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Structure and Optical Properties of Flame-Generated Soot, [1995] (Box 8)
    - Velocity/Mixture Fraction Statistics of Round, Self-Preserving, Buoyant Turbulent Plumes November 1995 (Box 8)
    - Velocity Statistics of Round, Fully Developed, Buoyant Turbulent Plumes February 1995 (Box 8)
  - 1996
    - CM-1 Pre-ship Review Process: LSP Assessment of Mission Success July 17, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Combustion Fluid Mechanics (Tools and Methods) November 19-20, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Effects of Hydrodynamics on Soot Formation in Laminar Opposed-Jet Diffusion Flames July-August 1996 (Box 8)
    - Flame/ Stretch Interactions in Laminar and Turbulent Premixed Flames December 6-7, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Distortion and Drop Formation Transitions at the Surface of Turbulent Liquids 1996 (Box 8)
    - Hydrodynamic Suppression of Soot Emissions in Laminar Diffusion Flames January-February 1996 (Box 8)
    - Markstein Numbers and Unstretched Laminar Burning Velocities of Wet Carbon Monoxide Flames, (incomplete) January 15-18, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Measured and Predicted Properties of Wet Carbon Monoxide/ Air Flames December 1996 (Box 8)
    - Structure and State Relationships of Laminar Soot-Free Hydrocarbon-Fueled Diffusion Flames December 1996 (Box 8)
    - Refractive Indices at Visible Wavelengths of Soot Emitted From Buoyant Turbulent Diffusion Flames, February / October 1996 (Box 8)
    - Refractive Indices of Overfire Soot in Large Buoyant Turbulent Diffusion Flames October 1996 (Box 8)
    - Spray Combustion Phenomena July 23, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Spray Formation at the Free Surface of Turbulent Bow Sheets June 1996 (Box 8)
    - Temporal Properties of Secondary Drop Breakup June 4-6, 1996 (Box 8)
  - 1997
    - Flame Stretch Interactions of Laminar Premixed Hydrogen/ Air Flames at Normal Temperature and Pressure 1997 (Box 8)
    - Generalized State Relationships of Laminar Permanently-Blue, Opposed-Jet Hydrocarbon-Fueled Diffusion Flames July 1997 (Box 8)
    - LSP Science Results October 28, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Measured and Predicted Properties of Hydrocarbon/ Air Flames at Various Pressures April 23-28, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Soot Formation in Freely-Propagating Laminar Premixed Flames May 1997 (Box 8)
    - The Structure and Breakup Properties of Natural and Technological Sprays November 11, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Turbulent Primary Drop Breakup in Bow Sprays 1997 (Box 8)
  - 1998
    - Aerodynamic Primary Breakup at the Surface of Nonturbulent Round Liquid Jets in Crossflow, January 12-15-1998 (Box 8)
    - Atomization and Spray Combustion (includes photos) January 15, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Atomization Physical Phenomena: Primary and Secondary Liquid Breakup in Sprays March 11-12, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Effects of Pressure and Nitrogen Dilution on Flame/ Stretch Interactions of Laminar Premixed H2/O2/N2 Flames 1998 (Box 8)
    - Flame Stretch Interactions of Premixed Alkane and Alcohol/ Air Flames May 28, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Mixing Structure of Plane Self-Preserving Buoyant Turbulent Plumes June 15-18, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Observations of Deformation and Breakup of Nonturbulent Round Liquid Jets in Gaseous Crossflows May 17-20, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Secondary Breakup and Turbulence Interactions of Drops June 29-July 1, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Shapes of Non-buoyant Round Luminous Hydrocarbon/ Air Laminar Jet Diffusion Flames May 24, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Sooting Limits of Outwardly-Propagating Spherical Laminar Premixed Flames, (includes photos, but no paper) August 1998 (Box 8)
    - Space Shuttle Observations of Soot-Containing Laminar Jet Diffusion Flames February 18, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Temporal Properties of Secondary Drop Breakup in the Bag Breakup Regime 1998 (Box 8)
  - 1999
    - Breakup Lengths of Turbulent Liquid Jets in Still Gases January 1999 (Box 8)
    - Breakup of Turbulent Liquid Jets in Still Gases June 28-July 1, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Development of Buoyant Turbulent Plumes from Round Sources in Cross Flows July 5-8, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Flame-Flow Interactions During Combustion of Gases November 21-23, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Flame Shapes of Luminous Non-buoyant Laminar Coflowing Jet Diffusion Flames March 15-17, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Flame/ Stretch Interactions of Heavy Hydrocarbon/ O/N Flames January 1999 (Box 8)
    - Hydrodynamic Suppression of Soot Formation in Laminar Coflowing Jet Diffusion Flames December 1999 (Box 8)
    - Interwake Turbulence Properties of Homogeneous Particle-Laden Flows June 28-July 1, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Laminar Soot Processes May 18-20, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Laminar Soot Processes Experiment February 18, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Liquid Atomization in Multiphase Flows: A Review June 28-July 1, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Mixture Fraction Statistics of Plane Self-Preserving Buoyant Turbulent Adiabatic Wall Plumes November 1999 (Box 8)
    - Observations of Non-buoyant Laminar Diffusion Flames Using Space Shuttle Facilities December 6, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Preferential-Diffusion Effects on Premixed Hydrogen-Fueled Flames: Measurements and Predictions June 1999 (Box 8)
    - Primary Breakup of Nonturbulent Round Liquid Jets in Gas Crossflows, (includes photos) 1999 (Box 8)
    - Scattering and Extinction Properties of Overfire Soot in Large Buoyant Turbulent Diffusion Flames August 15-17, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Soot Formation in Laminar Premixed Flames May 18-20, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Soot Growth in Laminar Premixed Flames (student thesis committee research) March 26, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Structure and Soot Properties of Laminar Jet Diffusion Flames June 27-July 2, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Structure of Turbulent Adiabatic Wall Plumes Along Plane Vertical Smooth Surfaces July 5-8, 1999 (Box 8)
    - The Structure, Optical, and Radiative Properties of Soot in Flame Environments: A Review March 15-19, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Temporal Properties of Multimode Secondary Droplet Breakup January 11-14, 1999 (Box 8)
  - 2000
    - Combustion Module-2: Laminar Soot Processes (LSP) August 15-17, 2000 (Box 9)
    - Continuous-Phase Properties of Homogeneous Particle-Laden Turbulent Flows September 27, 2000 (Box 9)
    - Deformation and Drag Properties of Nonturbulent Round Liquid Jets in Uniform Crossflows January 2000 (Box 9)
    - Drop-Gas Interactions in Dense Sprays June 12-14, 2000 (Box 9)
    - Extinction and Scattering of Soot Emitted from Turbulent Diffusion Flames for Wavelengths of 250-5200 nm August 2000 (Box 9)
    - Interwake Turbulence Properties of Homogeneous Dilute Particle-Laden Flows June 2000 (Box 9)
    - Laminar Soot Processes (LSP) Overview October 4, 2000 (Box 9)
    - Measurements and Predictions of Flame/ Stretch Interactions of Hydrogen-Fueled Laminar Premixed Flames January 10-13, 2000 (Box 9)
    - Measurements and Predictions of Turbulence Generation in Homogeneous Particle-Laden Flows January 2000 (Box 9)
    - Rates and Outcomes of Secondary Breakup December 5, 2000 (Box 9)
    - Shapes of Non-buoyant Laminar Jet Diffusion Flames at Soot-Free and Smoke-Point Conditions April 2000 (Box 9)
    - Smoke-Point Properties of Non-Buoyant Laminar Jet Diffusion Flames 2000 (Box 9)
    - [Soot Control Technologies], circa 2000 (Box 9)
    - Soot Growth and Oxidation in Laminar Acetylene/ Air Diffusion Flames at Atmospheric Pressure April 2000 (Box 9)
    - Soot Growth and Oxidation in Laminar Diffusion Flames April 16-18, 2000 (Box 9)
    - Structure and Mixing Properties of Unsteady Round Non-buoyant Turbulent Jets and Puffs in Still Gases November 5-10, 2000 (Box 9)
    - Turbulence Generation in Homogeneous Particle-Laden Flows April 2000 (Box 9)
    - Turbulent Primary Breakup of Round and Plane Liquid Jets in Still Air January 2000 (Box 9)
    - Velocity Statistics of Plane Self-Preserving Buoyant Turbulent Adiabatic Wall Plumes 2000 (Box 9)
  - 2001
    - [Untitled], Clean Air Conference July 9-12, 2001 (Box 9)
    - [Untitled], US-NSF Seminar, Italy September 2001 (Box 9)
    - Early Soot Oxidation in Hydrocarbon-Fueled Laminar Diffusion Flames at Atmospheric Pressure February 2001 (Box 9)
    - Effects of Fire Suppressants on Hydrogen-Fueled Laminar Premixed Flames February 2001 (Box 9)
    - Electric Field Distribution in a Spherical Diffusion Flame Region 2001 (Box 9)
    - Experimental Simulations of Buoyant Turbulent Plumes from Pool Fires November 12-16, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Flame/ Stretch Interactions of Premixed Hydrogen-Fueled Flames: Measurements and Predictions 2001 (Box 9)
    - Mechanisms of Fire Suppression by Halons and Halon Replacements: A Review, (incomplete) July 9-12, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Micro-G and You: Space Research and Benefits on Earth Physical Sciences/ Combustion, (includes photos) May 2, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Non-buoyant Ethylene/ Air Spherical Diffusion Flames in Concentric DC Electric Fields 2001 (Box 9)
    - Overview of NASA Research in Combustion Science April 18, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Primary Breakup of Turbulent Liquids May 2001 (Box 9)
    - Self-Preserving Properties of Unsteady Round Non-buoyant Turbulent Starting Jets and Puffs in Still Fluids November 11-16, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Search for the Turbulent Mixing Mechanism Within Sprays September 2001 (Box 9)
    - Soot and Smoke Points of Round Laminar Jet Diffusion Flames March 2001 (Box 9)
    - Soot Formation and Oxidation in Laminar Premixed and Diffusion Flames September 2001 (Box 9)
    - Soot Growth in Hydrocarbon-Fueled Laminar Diffusion Flames at Atmospheric Pressure January 2001 (Box 9)
    - Soot Research in Combustion Science: Introduction and Review of Current Work January 2001 (Box 9)
    - Soot Surface Growth in Laminar Hydrocarbon/ Air Diffusion Flames at Atmospheric Pressure January 8-11, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Suppression of Soot Formation and Shapes of Laminar Jet Diffusion Flames May 22-24, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Surface Properties of Turbulent Liquid Jets in Still Air November 2001 (Box 9)
    - Temporal Properties of Secondary Drop Breakup in the Multimode Breakup Regime 2001 (Box 9)
    - Turbulence Generation in Homogeneous Polydisperse Particle-Laden Flows November 2001 (Box 9)
  - 2002
    - Deformation and Drag Properties of Round Drops Subjected to Shock Wave Disturbances, January 14-17-2002 (Box 9)
    - Diffusion-Flame/ Electric-Field Interactions in a Spherically Symmetric System January 14-17, 2002 (Box 9)
    - Dynamics of Secondary Drop Breakup-A Rate Controlling Process in Dense Sprays July 2002 (Box 9)
    - Effects of Halons and Halon Replacements on Hydrogen-Fueled Laminar Premixed Fames September-October 2002 (Box 9)
    - Physical, Optical and Reactive Properties of Soot in Flame Environments March 2002 (Box 9)
    - Properties of Buoyant Turbulent Thermals and Plumes in Still and Crossflowing Environments June 24-27, 2002 (Box 9)
    - Round Turbulent Puffs and Buoyant Thermals in Uniform Crossflows June 2002 (Box 9)
    - Round Turbulent Starting Jets and Plumes in Uniform Crossflows November 24-26, 2002 (Box 9)
    - Soot Formation and Early Oxidation in Laminar Diffusion Flames at Atmospheric Pressure February 2002 (Box 9)
    - Soot Formation and Oxidation in Premixed and Non-premixed Flame Environments May 2002 (Box 9)
    - Soot Surface Growth and Oxidation Properties of Premixed and Non-premixed Flames April 18, 2002 (Box 9)
    - Turbulence Generation by Drops in Dense Sprays November 7, 2002 (Box 9)
  - 2003
    - Effects of Pressure on the Mechanisms of Soot Formation and Oxidation in Laminar Diffusion Flames, (student thesis committee research) November 5, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Experimental Simulations of the Overfire Flow of Round Turbulent Starting and Interrupted Non-premixed Fires March 14, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Experimental Study of the Breakup of Nonturbulent Round Liquid Jets in Gaseous Crossflows November 2003 (Box 9)
    - Laminar Soot Processes (LSP) Experiment: Findings From Ground-Based Measurements June 3-6, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Laminar Soot Processes (LSP) Experiment: Findings From Space Flight Measurements 2003 (Box 9)
    - LSP Flight Talk 2003 (Box 9)
    - Non-buoyant Round Hydrocarbon-Fueled Laminar Jet Diffusion Flames in Still Air October 26-29, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Primary Breakup of Turbulent and Nonturbulent Liquid Jets June 11-13, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Properties of Nonturbulent Round Liquid Jets in Uniform Gaseous Crossflow (includes photos) November 2003 (Box 9)
    - Round Turbulent Thermals, Puffs, Starting Plumes and Starting Jets in Uniform Crossflow December 2003 (Box 9)
    - Self-Preserving Properties of Unsteady Round Buoyant Turbulent Plumes and Thermals in Still Fluids October 2003 (Box 9)
    - Soot Processes in Non-buoyant Laminar Jet Diffusion Flames: A Paradigm for Soot Processes in Practical Non-premixed Flames July 27-August 1, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Soot Surface Growth and Oxidation in Diffusion Flames at Subatmospheric and Atmospheric Pressures January 6-9, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Soot Surface Reaction Properties of Hydrocarbon-Fueled Laminar Jet Diffusion Flames April 25, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Soot Nucleation in Laminar Premixed and Non-premixed Flames July 31, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Structure and Soot Surface Reaction Properties of Laminar Diffusion Flames at 0.1-1.0 ATM March 16-19, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Structure and Soot Surface Reaction Properties of Laminar Jet Diffusion Flames at Various Pressures 2003 (Box 9)
    - Structure of Continuous-Phase Turbulence Within Dense Dispersed Flows May 1, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Washington Meeting Presentation November 13, 2003 (Box 9)
  - 2004
    - Breakup of Aerated-Liquid Jets in Supersonic Crossflows January 5-8, 2004 (Box 9)
    - Combustion Science in Space: The Laminar Soot Processes (LSP) Experiment April 14, 2004 (Box 9)
    - Effects of Chemically-Passive Suppressants on Laminar Premixed Hydrogen/ Oxygen/ Nitrogen/ Suppressant Flames September 2004 (Box 10)
    - Effects of Flow Properties on Soot Formation and Oxidation Rates in Flame Environments January 5-8, 2004 (Box 10)
    - Identifying and Rationalizing Technical "Sweet Spots": Fundamental Science and Technology October 5, 2004 (Box 10)